Viewers all over the world, receive your portion.
Be delivered!
Be healed!
Whatever sickness, whatever name they call it -
never a sickness Jesus cannot heal, never a burden Jesus cannot bear,
never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B.
Joshua Touch The Screen By Faith, In Jesus' Name
Are you on the sickbed?
Dry bones, rise again.
All spirits operating in your system, be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Be cast out in the name of Jesus!
All spirits operating in your system, ears, throat, tongue, head, be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Be cast out, in the name of Jesus!
Come out!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Let there be light in your soul.
Let there be light in your system.
Let there be light in your spirit.
Let there be light in your flesh.
Let there be light in your blood.
Let there be light in your fluids.
Let there be light in your bones.
Let there be light in your muscles.
Let there be light in your womb.
Let there be light, in the name of Jesus Christ!
It is well.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Right now, begin to commit your business, your career.
Good Morning, my career. It is a new dawn.
My future, Good Morning. It is a new dawn.
My destiny, Good Morning. It is a new dawn.
It is a new dawn. Good Morning!
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
Engage with God!
We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more
of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up to date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives,
Changing nations and Changing the world
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 21/07/2018 + Robert